cdcovers.to 2006-09-01

# CDcovers.to - cd covers, music and software

Audio • Bollywood • CDi • DreamCast • DVD • Gameboy Advance • Gamecube • Karaoke • MiniDisc • PC • Playstation • Playstation 2 • PSP • VHS • Video CD • Xbox • Xbox 360

**Privacy policy**

CDcovers.to respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use CDcovers.to's search engine services. Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy policy.

**CDcovers.to and cookies**

Upon your first visit to CDcovers.to, CDcovers.to sends a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. CDcovers.to uses cookies to improve the quality of our service and to understand our user base more. CDcovers.to does this by storing user preferences in cookies. CDcovers.to will not disclose its cookies to third parties.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Beaware, however, that some parts of the CDcovers.to Search Service may not function properly if you refuse cookies.

**Third party advertising**

We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/).

**Third party cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**What information do we collect?**

CDcovers.to does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. CDcovers.to notes and saves information such as IP address and country code. That information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users. For example, CDcovers.to may use your IP address or browser language to determine which language to use when showing search results or advertisements.

**Links to other sites**

The sites displayed as search results or linked to by CDcovers.to Search Services are developed by people over whom CDcovers.to exercises no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. CDcovers.to may choose to exhibit its search results in the form of a "URL redirecter." When CDcovers.to uses a URL redirecter, if you click on a URL from a search result, information about the click is sent to CDcovers.to, and CDcovers.to in turn sends you to the site you clicked on.

**With whom does CDcovers.to share information?**

CDcovers.to may share information about you with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we only divulge aggregate information about our users and will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent. For example, we may disclose how frequently the average CDcovers.to user visits CDcovers.to.

**Your consent and changes to the privacy policy**

By using the CDcovers.to Search Services and our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy and to our Terms of Service Policy. CDcovers.to may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Who can I ask if I have additional questions?**

Feel free to contact us any time and we'll answer any additional questions you may have. Our email address is [webmaster@cdcovers.to](mailto:webmaster@cdcovers.to).
